Lloyd Wright papers LSC.1561
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Blueprints, plans, drawings, photos, renderings, and other material
  - Handley, Alan - Remodel 3003 Runyon Canyon Rd., Hollywood, 1965, 1966; Project No. 321 (Box 160, Box 686)
    Blueprints: Box 160
    Plans/Drawings: Box 686
  - Hanna, Phil - Residence St. Andrews Dr., Chevy Chase, 1933; Project No. 75 (Box 155, Box 377)
    Blueprints: Box 155
    Plans/Drawings: Box 377
  - Hare, Dr. Robert - Remodel 642 Perugia Way, Bel Air, 1962; Project No. 300 (Box 194, Box 272, Box 554)
    Blueprints: Boxes 194, 272
    Plans/Drawings: Box 554
  - Harris, Dr. Leonard - Residence Orange County, Calif., 1963; Project No. 305 (Box 280, Box 563, Box 673)
    Blueprints: Box 280
    Plans/Drawings: Box 563
  - Harris, Elmer - No description No address, 1935; Project No. 93 (Box 398)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 398
  - Hartford, Huntington - Drawings by Frank Lloyd Wright [Copies], no date (Box 664)
  - Hartford, Huntington - Fine arts galleries 2000 N. Fuller Ave., 1953, 1954; Project No. 236 (Box 168, Box 176, Box 221, Box 506, Box 669)
    Blueprints: Boxes 168, 176, 221
    Plans/Drawings: Box 506
  - Hartford, Huntington - Hotel 2000 Fuller Ave., 1947; Project No. 182 (Box 107, Box 505)
    Blueprints: Box 107
    Plans/Drawings: Box 505
  - Hartford, Huntington - Outpost Club 2000 N. Fuller Ave., 1946; Project No. 181 (Box 281, Box 504, Box 287)
    Blueprints: Boxes 281, 287
    Plans/Drawings: Box 504
  - Hartford, Huntington - Pool pavilion 2000 N. Fuller Ave., 1950; Project No. 200 (Box 114, Box 503)
    Blueprints: Box 114
    Plans/Drawings: Box 503
  - Hartford, Huntington - Rustic Canyon projects 2000 Rustic Canyon Road, 1950; Project No. 204 (Box 187, Box 196, Box 508, Box 507)
    Blueprints: Boxes 187, 196
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 508, 507
  - Hartford, Huntington - Rustic Canyon tracings Rustic Canyon, no date; Project No. 204 (Box 509)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 509
  - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square - model drawings Genesee & Spaulding at Wilshire, 1951; Project No. 222 (Box 497)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 497
  - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square - annex & parking bldg. Genesee & Spaulding at Wilshire, 1951; Project No. 228 (Box 161, Box 188, Box 499, Box 502)
    Blueprints: Boxes 161, 188
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 502, 499
  - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square - diagonal axis general studies Genesee & Spaulding at Wilshire, 1952; Project No. 227 (Box 188)
    Blueprints: Box 188
  - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square - diagonal axis study #1 Genesee & Spaulding at Wilshire, 1952; Project No. 224 (Box 117, Box 188, Box 157, Box 498)
    Blueprints: Boxes 117, 188, 157
    Plans/Drawings: Box 498
  - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square - diagonal axis study #2 Genesee & Spaulding at Wilshire, 1952; Project No. 226 (Box 188, Box 500)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 500
  - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square - elevator lobby, revised Genesee & Spaulding at Wilshire, 1951; Project No. 223 (Box 188, Box 501)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 501
  - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square, Inc. arena plan Genesee & Spaulding at Wilshire, 1949, 1950; Project No. 207 (Box 162, Box 163, Box 494, Box 496)
    Blueprints: Boxes 162, 163
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 496, 494
  - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square Genesee & Spaulding at Wilshire, 1950; Project No. 207 (Box 603, Box 669)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 603
  - Hartford, Huntington - Theatre Square Spaulding & Genesee at Wilshire, 1950; Project No. 208 (Box 495, Box 676)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 495
    Photos: Box 676
  - Headly, George W. - Residence 701 Stone Canyon Dr., Beverly Hills, 1944; Project No. 142 (Box 173, Box 442)
    Blueprints: Box 173
    Plans/Drawings: Box 442
  - Healy, Mr. & Mrs. P.J. - Cabinet work 565 Perugia Way, Los Angeles, 1950; Project No. 283 (Box 550)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 550
  - Healy, Mr. & Mrs. P.J. - Gate & barbecue remodel 565 Perugia Way, Los Angeles, 1951, 1952; Project No. 219 (Box 482)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 482
  - Healy, Mr. & Mrs. P.J. - Potting shelter 565 Perugia Way, Los Angeles, 1951; Project No. 212 (Box 481)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 481
  - Healy, Mr. & Mrs. P.J. - Residence 565 Perugia Way, 1949; Project No. 196 (Box 167, Box 480, Box 671)
    Blueprints: Box 167
    Plans/Drawings: Box 480
  - Hearn, Eddie - Remodel & addition 10511 Selkirk Lane, West Los Angeles, 1954; Project No. 239 (Box 248, Box 515)
    Blueprints: Box 248
    Plans/Drawings: Box 515
  - Heifetz, Jascha - Beach house Malibu Road, 1960; Project No. 289 (Box 265)
    Blueprints: Box 265
  - Heifetz, Jascha - Pavilion at studio 1520 Gilcrest Dr., Beverly Hills, Calif., 1951; Project No. 206 (Box 192, Box 485)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 485
  - Heifetz, Jascha - Residence 18 Harbor Island, Newport Beach, Calif., 1939; Project No. 117 (Box 118, Box 486, Box 673)
    Blueprints: Box 118
    Plans/Drawings: Box 486
  - Heifetz, Jascha - Studio & remodel 1520 Gilcrest Dr., Beverly Hills, Calif., 1948; Project No. 177 (Box 116, Box 487)
    Blueprints: Box 115
    Plans/Drawings: Box 403
  - Heifetz, Jascha - Studio Gilcrest Dr., Los Angeles, 1946; Project No. 177 (Box 690)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 690
  - Helen's adobe house no address, no date (Box 679)
  - Henderson - Gymnasium Los Angeles, 1930; Project No. 76 (Box 168, Box 614)
    Blueprints: Box 168
    Plans/Drawings: Box 614
  - Henrichs, Henry F. - Press building Litchfield, Illinois, 1938; Project No. 108 (Box 115, Box 403)
  - Henry, Burns - Residence Glenoak Hills, Rancho, Calif., 1974; Project No. 351 (Box 190, Box 211, Box 599)
    Blueprints: Boxes 190, 211
    Plans/Drawings: Box 599
  - Henry, Burns - Residence Glenoak Hills, Rancho, Calif., 1974; Project No. 352 (Box 210, Box 598, Box 668)
    Blueprints: Box 210
    Plans/Drawings: Box 598
  - Hollywood Bowl Asso. - Hollywood Bowl Shells 1 & 2 Highland Ave., 1927, 1928; Project No. 11 (Box 156, Box 608, Box 678)
    Blueprints: Box 156
    Plans/Drawings: Box 608
  - Hollywood Bowl Asso. - Robin Hood, Julius Caesar & proposed tea garden Highland Ave., 1923; Project No. 12 (Box 120, Box 609)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 609
  - Hollywood Bowl - Second shell Hollywood, Calif., 1928; Project No. 11 (Box 643)
  - Holmby Park - Art display Holmby Park, West Los Angeles, 1951; Project No. 214 (Box 484)
    Plans/Drawing: Box 484
  - Honeycutt, Mrs. & Mrs. - Residence and lancscaping Los Altos Park, Long Beach, Calif., 1953-1954; Project No. 231 (Box 141, Box 519)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 519
  - Howard, Frank - Remodel & additions to pool and ramadas 16475 Garvin Dr., Encino, Calif., 1957; Project No. 255 (Box 532, Box 669)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 532
  - Howard, Frank - Remodel & additions 16475 Garvin Dr., Encino, Calif., 1954; Project No. 238 (Box 256)
    Blueprints: Box 256
  - Howard, Frank - Remodel bedroom, garage, landscaping 16821 Oakview, Encino, Calif., 1957; Project No. 265 (Box 233, Box 524)
    Blueprints: Box 233
    Plans/Drawings: Box 524
  - Howe, Herbert - Residence 513 Roxbury, Beverly Hills, 1925; Project No. 20 (Box 128, Box 335)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 335
  - Howland, Jobyna - Residence 502 N. Crescent Dr., 1932; Project No. 72 (Box 677)
  - Howland, Jobyna - Residence 502 N. Crescent Dr., 1933; Project No. 74 (Box 134, Box 378, Box 646, Box 672)
    Blueprints: Box 134
    Plans/Drawings: Box 378
    Other: Box 646
  - Hulet, Dr. William Granada Blvd., Coral Gables, 1963, 1965
    SEE: Pheiffer, John F. residence
  - Huntington Portal - Hotel apts., motel marina, marina esplanade, condominium Sunset Bay, Surfside, Calif., 1962; Project No. 297 (Box 244, Box 294, Box 549, Box 638)
    Blueprints: Boxes 244, 294
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 549, 638
  - Imperial Hotel Tokyo, no date (Box 679)
  - Institute of Mentalphysics - Cafeteria & cottages Yucca Valley, Calif., 1954; Project No. 240 (Box 144, Box 227, Box 228, Box 229, Box 288, Box 293, Box 513)
    Blueprints: Boxes 144, 227, 228, 229, 293, 288
    Plans/Drawing: Boxes 513
  - Institute of Mentalphysics - Caravansary, admin. bldg., & residence of Dr. Dingle Yucca Valley, Calif., 1946; Project Nos. 158A & B (Box 653)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 653
  - Institute of Mentalphysics - Caravansary, administration building, site plan Yucca Valley, Calif., 1946; Project No. 158A & B (Box 149, Box 184, Box 648, Box 669)
    Blueprints: Boxes 149, 184
    Plans/Drawings: Box 648
    Photos: Box 669
  - Institute of Mentalphysics - Cottage and cottage terrace Yucca Valley, Calif., 1954 (Box 672)
  - Institute of Mentalphysics - Preceptory & sanctuary Yucca Valley, Calif., 1957; Project No. 253 (Box 182, Box 522)
    Blueprints: Box 182
    Plans/Drawings: Box 522
  - Institute of Mentalphysics - Temple of Reverence Yucca Valley, Calif., no date; Project No. 251 ? (Box 654)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 654
  - Inventions Various, no date; Project No. 364 (Box 621)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 621
  - Iredell, Russell - [Untitled] Lithograph, 1924 (Box 645)
  - Jacker - Residence 1265 Oakridge Ave., Glendale, Calif., 1957; Project No. 259 (Box 534)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 534
  - Jacobi, Jerome - Dr. Storer remodel 8161 Hollywood Blvd., Hollywood, 1970; Project No. 343 (Box 593)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 593
  - Jester, Ralph - Residence Lot 73, tract 14500, Portuguese Bend, Palos Verdes, 1949; Project No. 187 (Box 275, Box 477)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 477
  - Johnson, Beverly - Residence 7017 Senalda Rd., Los Angeles, 1963; Project No. 309 (Box 316, Box 637, Box 344, Box 683, Box 673)
    Blueprints: Box 316
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 637, 344, 683
  - Jones, Carol - Furniture No address, 1929; Project No. 53 (Box 178, Box 356)
    Blueprints: Box 178
    Plans/Drawings: Box 356
  - Jones, Felix, Mr. & Mrs. - Residence Valley St., Burbank, 1937; Project No. 105 (Box 215, Box 405)
    Blueprints: Box 215
    Plans/Drawings: Box 405
  - Jones, Frank, Mr. & Mrs. - Residence Lorencita Dr., Covina, 1950; Project No. 201 (Box 491)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 491
  - Jones, Frank - Residence 10503 Roundtree Rd., 1944; Project No. 143 (Box 178, Box 448)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 448
  - Jones, Grover - Residence Brentwood, Calif., 1927; Project No. 42 (Box 360)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 360
  - Jones, R. Lloyd & Mary - Grave rubbings, no date (Box 619)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 619
  - Joshua tree Photo by Fred Rencher, no date (Box 674)
  - Joshua Tree National Park - No description Joshua Tree, Calif., 1955; Project No. 246 (Box 526)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 526
  - Jowdy, Moudary - Remodel 2255 Verde Oak Dr., Hollywood, 1964; Project No. 314 (Box 234, Box 354)
    Blueprints: Box 234
    Plans/Drawings: Box 354
  - Justice, Jack - Abstract design Painting, 1962 (Box 208, Box 644)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 208
  - Justice, Jack - Global simulator Ventura, Calif., 1977; Project No. 359 (Box 119, Box 620)
    Blueprints: Box 119
    Plans/Drawings: Box 620
  - Kanin, Mrs. Sadie - Residence 240 Acari Dr., Los Angeles, 1953; Project No. 234 (Box 518)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 518
  - Karasik, Jacob - Pencilled revisions - obsolete [Beverly Hills], 1960 (Box 320)
    Blueprints: Box 320
  - Karasik, Jacob - Residence 436 Spalding Dr., Beverly Hills, 1960; Project No. 280 (Box 215, Box 538, Box 673)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 538
  - Karasik, Jacob - Residence 436 Spalding Dr., Beverly Hills, 1953 (Box 540)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 540
  - Karasik, S.K. - Residence - by Jack Justice No address, 1961; Project No. 363 (Box 208)
  - Kasher, Charles - Remodel of Samuel House 2255 Verde Oak Dr., Los Angeles, 1973; Project No. 349 (Box 252, Box 594)
    Blueprints: Box 252
    Plans/Drawings: Box 594
  - Kaufman, Edgar J. - Residence by FLW Bear Run, Pa., 1936 (Box 659)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 659
  - Kaufman, Louis - Remodel & addition 835 Westholme Ave., West Los Angeles, 1959; Project No. 278 (Box 217)
    Blueprints: Box 217
  - Kaufman, Louis - Remodel 835 Westholme Ave., West Los Angeles, 1957; Project No. 257 (Box 217)
  - Kaufman, Louis - Residence remodel 8137 Blackburn Ave. & 835 Westholme Ave., 1935; Project No. 89 (Box 217, Box 383)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 383
  - Kaye, Harold E. - Residence #2 Comstock Ave., Westwood, 1945; Project No. 150 (Box 436)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 436
  - Kaye, Harold E. - Residence remodel Comstock Ave., Westwood, 1941; Project No. 137 (Box 127, Box 235, Box 418, Box 669)
    Blueprints: Boxes 127, 235
    Plans/Drawings: Box 418
  - Kellogg Farms - Ranch & farmstead Alemont, Nevada, 1940; Project No. 198 (Box 685)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 685
  - Kellogg, Lois II - Perchino Breeding Farms Pahrump Valley, Nevada, 1941; Project No. 138 (Box 249)
    Blueprints: Box 249
  - Kellogg, Lois II - Ranch development Banning, Calif., 1931; Project No. 69 (Box 137, Box 365)
    Blueprints: Box 137
    Plans/Drawings: Box 365
  - Kent, Rockwell - Drawing Ink, 1921 (Box 644)
  - King, Dr. Richard - Dental suite Huntington Beach, Calif., 1969; Project No. 337 (Box 153, Box 580)
    Blueprints: Box 153
    Plans/Drawings: Box 580
  - Komo, Shizue - Painting Slumbering eagle, no date (Box 646)
  - Kropp, Roy - Cascades Chardon Farms, Grayslake, Illinois, 1956; Project No. 252 (Box 212, Box 529)
    Blueprints: Box 212
    Plans/Drawings: Box 529
  - Kropp, Roy - Residence & carport Chardon Farms, Grayslake, Illinois, 1952; Project No. 220 (Box 212, Box 511)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 511
  - Kropp, Roy - Southwest air view No address, no date (Box 679)
  - Lair, Max - Apple Valley farm - Titles Apple Valley, Calif., 1965 (Box 669)
  - Lair, Max - Residence & subdivision Granite Mountain, Apple Valley, Calif., 1975; Project No. 355 (Box 272, Box 674, Box 668)
    Blueprints: Box 272
  - LaRue, Louis, Mr. & Mrs. - Residence 35201 Mulholland, Los Angeles, 1968; Project No. 332 (Box 111, Box 585)
    Blueprints: Box 111
    Plans/Drawings: Box 585
  - Lathwood, Jo - Studio 123 Ocean Way, Los Angeles, 1969 July (Box 116)
    Blueprints: Box 116
  - Laughton, Charles - Pool & dressing room 1825 North Curson Ave., Los Angeles, 1952; Project No. 213 (Box 180, Box 514)
    Blueprints: Box 180
    Plans/Drawings: Box 514
  - Lazarus, Mr. & Mrs. S.M. - Residence 4966 Ambrose Ave., Los Angeles, 1937; Project No. 97 (Box 204, Box 401)
    Blueprints: Box 204
    Plans/Drawings: Box 401
  - Leerdam - Glass design data No address, 1927; Project No. 38 (Box 348)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 348
  - Levand, Mr. & Mrs. Jack J. - Residence 1107 Wallace Ridge Rd., Beverly Hills, Calif., 1958; Project No. 267 (Box 181, Box 282, Box 539, Box 669)
    Blueprints: Boxes 181, 282
    Plans/Drawings: Box 539
  - Lewis, E.R. - Residence 2948 Graceland Way, Chevy Chase, 1926; Project No. 33 (Box 346)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 346
  - Lewis, Lionel - Residence 527 North Crescent Dr., 1941; Project No. 132 (Box 237, Box 423)
    Blueprints: Box 237
    Plans/Drawings: Box 423
  - Lincoln Fidelity Corp. - Apartments 10842 Magnolia Ave., Anaheim, 1964; Project No. 310 (Box 234, Box 241, Box 242, Box 269, Box 568, Box 567)
    Blueprints: Boxes 234, 241, 242, 269
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 568, 567
  - Lincoln Fidelity Corp. - La Jolla student housing La Jolla, Calif., 1964; Project No. 312 (Box 161, Box 566, Box 705)
    Blueprints: Box 161
    Plans/Drawings: Box 566
    Other: Box 705
  - Lincoln Fidelity Corp. - Terrace Park apartments Stanton, Calif., 1964; Project No. 360 (Box 673)
  - Lloyd Wright, Eric Wright, Tom Bradley Photo, 1974 (Box 674)
  - Loew, David Jr. - Residence 10357 Calvin Ave., 1944; Project No. 159 (Box 136, Box 452)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 452
  - Lombardi, Dr. John - Residence 804 Gatos Place, Palos Verdes, 1965; Project No. 318 (Box 152, Box 671)
    Blueprints: Box 152
  - Lombardi, Dr. John - Residence 804 Gatos Place, Palos Verdes, 1965; Project No. 318 (Box 183, Box 186, Box 196, Box 638, Box 681)
    Blueprints: Boxes 183, 186, 196
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 638, 681
  - Los Angeles County - Regional plan Los Angeles & vicinity, 1962-1964; Project No. 299 (Box 631, Box 668)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 631
  - Los Angeles - Bunker Hill redevelopment - 120 story building, parks, malls Bunker Hill, 1973; Project No. 350.5 (Box 595)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 595
  - Los Angeles - Library & central city study & clippings Los Angeles, 1969 Nov. (Box 646)
  - Los Angeles - Proposed civic center Los Angeles, 1925; Project No. 43 (Box 646, Box 651, Box 677)
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 646, 651
  - Lubsen, H.F. - Residence 1262 Rubio Ave., Altadena, 1940; Project No. 127 (Box 169, Box 426)
    Blueprints: Box 169
    Plans/Drawings: Box 426
  - Lumbleau, John - Residence 22158 Pacific Coast Hwy., Malibu, 1959; Project No. 282 (Box 285, Box 286, Box 541)
    Blueprints: Boxes 285, 286
    Plans/Drawings: Box 541
  - Mace, John L. - Residence (one story) 8292 Hollywood Blvd., 1958; Project No. 269 (Box 247, Box 548)
    Blueprints: Box 247
    Plans/Drawings: Box 548
  - Mamoulian, Rouben - Residence 1419 N. Beverly, 1941; Project No. 133 (Box 420, Box 669)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 420
  - Marks - Residence & remodel 710 Hilcrest, Beverly Hills, 1934; Project No. 81 (Box 390)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 390
  - Marple, Albert - Store front No address, 1929; Project No. 55 (Box 205, Box 357)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 357
  - Martin, Burn - Residence (proposed) Palm Springs, 1927; Project No. 44 (Box 215, Box 362)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 362
  - Mausoleum No address, 1924 (Box 611)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 611
  - McDowall, Louise - Residence 4937 Graceland Way, Chevy Chase, 1928; Project No. 47 (Box 148, Box 364)
    Blueprints: Box 148
    Plans/Drawings: Box 364
  - McManus - Cascade Club & Bassett Tennis Club No address, 1934; Project No. 83 (Box 646)
  - McManus - Residence & hotel Palm Springs, 1924, 1926; Project No. 16 (Box 616, Box 645)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 616
  - Metzler, Milton - Residence Camarillo, Calif., 1928; Project No. 45 (Box 294, Box 361)
    Blueprints: Box 294
    Plans/Drawings: Box 361
  - Mikules, Peter - Residence No address, 1949; Project No. 198 (Box 142, Box 489)
    Blueprints: Box 142
    Plans/Drawings: Box 489
  - Mile-high building by FLW Chicago, no date (Box 666)
  - Millard - Daniels - Residence Pasadena, 1926-1979 (Box 691)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 691
  - Millard, Alice - Residence & studio 645 Propsect, Crescent Way, Pasadena, 1926, 1932; Project No. 25 (Box 626)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 626
  - Millier, Arthur - [Untitled] Etchings, no date (Box 645)
  - Moore, Dr. Louis D. - Residence 504 Paseo Del Mar, Palos Verdes, 1956, 1967; Project No. 254 (Box 161, Box 536, Box 649, Box 675, Box 643)
    Plans/Drawings: Boxes 536, 649
  - Moorehead, Dr. S.I. - Residence addition Palos Verdes, 1967; Project No. 329 (Box 136, Box 574)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 574
  - Motor court Los Angeles, 1937; Project No. 98 (Box 415)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 415
  - Mount Olivet - Lutheran Church and additions Minneapolis, Minn., 1961; Project No. 290 (Box 189, Box 560, Box 671)
    Blueprints: Box 189
    Plans/Drawings: Box 560
  - Murphy Ranch - Additions for Mrs Jesse M. Murphy 2800 Rustic Canyon, 1934; Project No. 83.5 (Box 223)
  - Murphy Ranch - Garage unit Rustic Canyon, 1934 (Box 245, Box 246, Box 248, Box 267, Box 317)
    Blueprints: Boxes 245, 246, 248, 267, 317
  - Murphy Ranch - Maps, including Uplifters Club Rustic Canyon, 1934 - 35 (Box 253)
    Blueprints: Box 253
  - Murphy Ranch - Maps Rustic Canyon, 1934 - 35 (Box 254, Box 320)
    Blueprints: Boxes 254, 320
  - Murphy Ranch - Residence - Stevens residence, not constructed Rustic Canyon, no date (Box 318)
    Blueprints: Box 318
  - Murphy Ranch - Residence by Paul Williams Rustic Canyon, no date (Box 325, Box 327)
    Blueprints: Boxes 325, 327
  - Murphy Ranch - Survey originals - architects: Plummer, Wardman & Becket Rustic Canyon, 1934; Project No. 83.5 (Box 179)
    Blueprints: Box 179
  - Murphy Ranch - [no description] Rustic Canyon, 1934 (Box 238)
    Blueprints: Box 238
  - Murphy, Mrs. Jessie M. - Ranch additions - power house Rustic Canyon, no date; Project No. 83.5 (Box 374)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 374
  - Murray, Forest, Mrs. - Residence & garage No address, 1946; Project No. 165 (Box 454)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 454
  - Nabel, Josef - Garden pavilion 2323 La Mesa, Santa Monica, 1955; Project No. 241 (Box 138)
    Blueprints: Box 138
  - Nabel, Josef - Garden pavilion 2323 La Mesa, Santa Monica, 1970; Project No. 344 (Box 222)
  - Nabel, Josef - Residence 2223 La Mesa, Santa Monica, 1949; Project No. 194 (Box 138, Box 465, Box 673, Box 643)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 465
  - Nagel, Conrad - Market Monrovia & Arcadia, 1931; Project No. 66 (Box 145, Box 353)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 353
  - Navarro / Samuel - Residence 5609 Valley Oak Drive, 1928; Project No. 50, 50A (Box 231, Box 341, Box 671)
    Blueprints: Box 231
    Plans/Drawings: Box 341
  - Navarro, J.M. - Residence remodel no address, no date; Project No. 314 (Box 570)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 570
  - Navarro, Ramon - Samuel House addition 5609 Valley Oak Dr., 1931; Project No. 50A (Box 239, Box 130, Box 351)
    Blueprints: Boxes 239, 130
    Plans/Drawings: Box 351
  - Nelson, J.C. - Residence Los Angeles, 1926; Project No. 26 (Box 339)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 339
  - Nesbitt, John - Residence remodel - formerly Ennis residence 2655 Glendower Ave., 1940; Project No. 124 (Box 291, Box 428)
    Blueprints: Box 291
    Plans/Drawings: Box 428
  - Newman, Alfred - Furniture - boys' rooms 1 & 2 14148 Sunset Blvd., Los Angeles, 1951; Project No. 216 (Box 512)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 512
  - Newman, Alfred - Residence & remodel 624 N. Canon Dr., Beverly Hills, 1934; Project No. 82 (Box 155, Box 389, Box 672)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 389
  - Newman, Alfred - Residence 14148 Sunset Blvd., Pacific Palisades, 1949; Project No. 190 (Box 213, Box 214, Box 483, Box 671, Box 674, Box 677)
    Blueprints: Boxes 213, 214
    Plans/Drawings: Box 483
    Photos: Boxes 671, 674, 677
    Other: Box 677
  - Niles, Kenneth - Residence 2601 Rutherford, 1935; Project No. 86 (Box 150, Box 386)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 386
  - Oak Park Midwest Cultural Center - Cultural Center F.L.W. home & studio, Oak Park, Illinois, 1974; Project No. 353 (Box 596)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 596
  - Oak Park - Austin Gardens Oak Park, Illinois, 1977; Project No. 362 (Box 602)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 602
  - Oak Park - Frank Lloyd Wright festival banners Oak Park, Illinois, no date (Box 664)
  - Oasis Hotel Palm Springs, 1924-1926
    SEE: McManus
  - Oasis Hotel - Hotel bldg. Palm Springs, 1924; Project No. 16 (Box 108, Box 679)
    Blueprints: Box 108
    Photos: Boxes 679
  - Obler, Arch - Well drilling prior to residence, sketch & plans Decker Road, Mulholland Hwy., 1940; Project No. 126 (Box 251, Box 427)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 427
  - Office standards Various, no dates; Project No. 366A (Box 623)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 623
  - Oil derricks No address, 1930 (Box 679)
  - Oklahoma University - Lloyd Wright exhibit Norman, Okla., 1964; Project No. 311 (Box 238, Box 564)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 564
  - Olive Hill Foundation Hollywood, Calif., var. dates
    SEE: Barnsdall Park
  - Olive Hill Foundation - Education, social sciences, medical arts center Hollywood, 1944 (Box 644)
  - Olive Hill Foundation - Hollyhock House main entrace Hollywood, 1946; Project No. 170 (Box 644)
  - Olive Hill Foundation - Hollyhock House rendering [photographic copy] Hollywood, no date (Box 647)
    Other: Box 647
  - Olive Hill Foundation - Little dipper kindergarten by FLW [copy] Hollywood, 1921 (Box 663)
    Plans/Drawings: Box 663
  - Olive Hill Foundation - Reconstruct main building & gallery building by FLW Hollywood, 1946; Project No. 170 (Box 243)
    Blueprints: Box 243
  - Olive Hill Foundation - Reconstruct main building & proposed gallery by FLW Hollywood, 1946; Project No. 170 (Box 170, Box 206, Box 207, Box 694)
    Blueprints: Boxes 170, 206, 207
    Plans/Drawings: Box 694